This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home.
I'm
so truly grateful.
I ran into you on that day so long ago.
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes.
Till we knew we weren't alone.
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way.
And with it I know we'll rise.
We'll be flying up high.
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you want to fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever!
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
I don't matter where you
are, nothing is too far!
With our everlasting
problems, we'll reach it.
We are home from the horizon,
out on the edge of the world.
If there is a place that
I want to take you to?
Let's head for it then.
But as for the way we already know,
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated, It
crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun!
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together I'm
telling you in our path I trust that it
will lead us To another sea untarded
Cause now we are home On the horizon,
out on the edge of the world
There is a place I want to take
you to Let's head for it then
But after the way we already know
We promised it long ago
Looks like you're in
good shape to me Nice!
Poison made me hungry Should
I catch some more fish?
We got an island coming up
soon that'll take care of you.
So listen, I'll drop some
info while I still can.
Mama owns 34 islands around here?
In Whole Cake Island.
is right in the center
of them all. So many.
And just to give you a fair warning?
Each one of those islands has a minister.
that runs the show.
So all the islands and all the
water around here is Mama's kingdom.
We call it Kaku Land!
I understand.
Very sorry, sir.
I thought this was an enemy ship.
It was.
Until I stole it from the pirates myself.
I'll present it to Mama in
person once we're done here.
Oh!
Then am I to assume you have some
tantalizing treats hidden in there?
Of course I do.
In that case, I'm sure
Mama will be thrilled.
This is a surprise gift, though.
Oh, son, I don't want you reporting
a thing about this ship, got it?
Oh, good idea.
Very well, Pecan, sir.
Splendid work.
Oh, boy!
The fountain!
The houses! Look!
It's all made of chocolate!
A whole chocolate town?
Treats do come true!
Woo-hoo!
Yeah!
There's all sorts of people!
I love it! I love it!
This town is the greatest!
Check it out!
It's like water, only chocolate!
The Chaka found it a
fine choice, my good man!
Let's do it!
A chocolate bathhouse?
How does that work?
Chocolate clothes?
Can you eat them?
They bought my cover
story, but they bought me.
but we better not stay long just in case.
Get out!
So do what you gotta do, then scram.
We're in a rush anyway.
Ready to go?
Oh, wow, this is cute.
Oh, you're adorable.
Why thank you.
And what about me?
I hope it's pretty neat, too, right?
Yeah, I love it. Gorgeous.
Well, Brooke, do I look like a pirate?
Brooke...
What?
You want some more?
It's gonna take another day before
we make it to Whole Cake Island.
Be sure you get all you
need, especially food.
Okie Dock! Let's go!
Oh, I can't wait to see!
Pedro, have any binoculars
by chance? That's perfect!
Now let's see...
Wow, there's not just humans, but
all kinds of people living here, huh?
I even see minx!
It's like a wonderland! Damn straight!
That's what Mama's dream for
this country is all about!
Humans, minks, fishmen,
long arms, long legs, dwarves.
A land where every race in the world can
live together without discrimination.
Where all creations exist in harmony. Huh?
That's why she made this country? Uh-huh.
You're looking at Mama's
little slice of heaven.
Totoland!
A place befitting a ruler of her stature.
Right now, we're on Cacao Island,
run by the Minister of Chocolate.
The settlement is called Chocolatown.
What an awesome name!
I love it already!
Everything in town is made of chocolate.
That sounds delicious,
but can I eat it? Get out!
Yeah, you can eat all
the chocolate you want.
Otherwise, what would be the point?
Oh, boy!
But there's some important rules.
It's against the law to eat
the root-tile chocolates.
Otherwise, rain and snow
will get inside the houses.
Window Glass is the Minister
of Candy's jurisdiction?
And construction posts are handled
by the Minister of Biscuits?
and anything that isn't chocolate is
either private or public property.
I'm hungry.
Hey, were you listening?
It was too complicated, so no.
So, are the panties here
made of chocolate as well?
Of course they are.
I can't wait to see them.
We're not here for sightseeing.
Get the food and then get out. Get out.
I'll stay on the ship
since they know me here.
But I really love chocolate, so
you gotta get me some. Aye, aye.
Hey, stop stalling.
Put on your disguise, Straw Hat.
There were people waiting on you.
Lucy and Chopper already went to town.
What do you think's gonna happen if they
find out that I brought
Mama's enemies here?
You bunch of maniacs, we'll all die!
I wouldn't worry, we'll know
where they are soon enough.
There they are.
Oh, come on!
If it was just the chocolate
walls, we could easily build more.
What'd you eat the entire cafe, you fools?
You ate a ton of candy, too.
Not to mention marshmallows,
almonds, and jelly beans.
That's a crime.
No question.
This is Snackalism.
You're coming with me.
We'll sort this out at the station.
Yeah, but listen.
There's a good reason for
this. No? Spit it out.
That was too good.
The nerve of you. How seamless.
They'll be arrested at this rate.
I know, but we can't make a scene, Pedro.
What? Mr. Chaka Police?
Carpet.
Hey, it's flying that's neat. Carpet.
Oh, the owner. Hello, ma 'am.
Oh, not more trouble.
It's the owner of the cafe.
These D-gens have made
quite a mess of things.
I can't believe it.
How could you leave this much?
This isn't what we agreed to at all.
If you do a job, you have
to finish it properly.
Hey, do you know her?
No, I sure don't. That's weird.
Also, what's that on her shoulder?
What's the matter?
Are my chocolate-covered biscuits
and jam not good enough for you?
Here, try these.
Is it good? Yeah!
Mr.
Chaka Police, you must forgive me.
The truth is, the cafe
was about to expire.
I hired these two to eat
the whole building for me.
Oh, then pardon me.
I didn't know they were a demolition crew.
Sorry for the trouble, guys.
but next time you should
put a sign out when you're
doing your job and wait
for the customers to leave,
too.
Well, then, I'll be taking my leave.
Have a nice day, sir.
And I apologize for the
disturbance, everyone. Well, good.
They had me worried there.
I'm glad it wasn't a big deal.
Ah, almost forgot.
I heard about your engagement.
Congratulations, Lady Pudding.
I know your wedding day is coming
up soon, so don't overwork yourself.
Everyone in town wishes
nothing but the best for you.
That's very kind.
Why did she save them? I'm confused.
Maybe she's just really nice?
You sure got lucky.
Fortune favors the Pirate
King to be at every turn.
Captain Pedro!
It really is you, huh?
What a surprise!
It's been a while!
Why are you...
I'm sightseeing.
Don't tell anyone.
Uh, okay.
Nice chatting with you, I guess.
Do you know people in this town, Pedro?
We can talk later.
Uh-huh!
So your name's Pudding, huh? Well, thanks.
You saved our butts. Oh, no.
Don't say that.
I'm the one who should be
thanking all of you. Yeah, why?
Because of what you said.
that it was too delicious.
The chocolate at the cafe is the
new blend I just came up with.
Tell me, did it melt
in your mouth properly?
I added milk to cocoa butter and mixed
it with a high-purity beet sugar.
It was needed for three days
straight at 29 degrees precisely.
I don't understand any of that,
but your walls were awesome.
They were awesome.
That means all my hard work paid off.
I think I might cry.
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
How is this woman real?
She's too sweet.
You really like making chocolate, huh?
I gotta tell you, I'm
wild about sweet stuff.
In fact, just smelling chocolate
everywhere is enough to make me happy.
Eating's good, too. That's lovely.
I don't mean to be rude, especially
since you've been so generous?
but we really need to get going. I see.
That's a shame. Well?
How about you have a cup of tea first?
Something to follow up all those sweets.
Oh, why, that sounds perfect.
All right, this shouldn't take long.
Oh, my god.
She is such a sweet girl.
I'm sorry, I forgot to ask your name.
I'm Monkity Luffy.
I'm going to be a king of the world.
Seriously?
Huh?
Luffy?
How a songer will it be till
we have our tea for tea?
Only three days, Mama.
How long is that sound?
Tell me what is to be done with Jermason.
Soon we'll have him, Mama.
Couches, sofas, dressers, teapots.
All will be shall be,
all will be shall be,
all kings are lovely,
all kings are lovely, that design, divine,
and the prize, only mercy,
our remediants, take them,
but will flow if they resist,
mercy
ends!
They're mine.
Nice to go!
It's mine.
And the fruits!
It is mine.
Time to make a cake so good!
The finest cake you'll ever eat.
such sweet insanity.
Tea time. And hell?
what a party.
Is this some strawberry jam?
Either way, I don't give a damn!
And if you don't show your
sleep, they'll be low!
Social and bleeding is sacrificial!
Oh, it's a dreamland
with joy never ending!
Everyone is welcome,
our harmony is blending!
To the land!
Hmm i heard that he's here is he
truly near yes he is oh it's true
Your mind strong hat
Your name is Luffy?
That was a mistake!
Now that I look closer,
I do recognize you!
You're Straw Hat Luffy!
That's right!
And I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
We're all dead men walking now.
Wait a minute.
You people aren't really the
Straw Hat Pirates, are you?
Yep, that's us.
Sanji's crewmates are here?
It can't be true.
I just told you it is.
Are you even listening to me?
Wait, do you know Sanji?
What? What?
You're seriously the lady
who's supposed to marry Sanji?
Big mom is your mom?
It is her. No way.
Sanji's so lucky.
What a beautiful bride to be.
You said bride.
I don't understand.
And...
you aren't even Mama's allies.
How did you get through Tart's security?
If she finds out you're here, you'll...
you'll all be killed.
You shouldn't have come to her territory.
She's a very scary pirate. Huh?
Huh?
And here's the Straw Hats, so
you're all scary pirates, too!
Help me!
Relax, you're okay.
We won't attack you.
Hey, Luffy, want me to kill her?
What did I say?
Back off!
So, that's what you want.
You plan to take him away.
I knew it, Mama is forcing him.
This is the way she does business.
In order to strengthen her pirate group,
she often arranges
marriages for her children.
There's no hope.
All of us have given up
on marrying for love.
You can either accept it or run away.
One of my older sisters did the latter.
She ran off to sea a while
back in search of a husband.
Of her choosing.
I hope you'll pardon my curiosity,
but the invitation says you're the
35th daughter of the Charlottes?
There can't be that many, right?
That'd be silly.
No.
There are 39 of us
girls, and 46 boys, too.
So Mama's actually got
85 children altogether.
That's a lot of kids! That many?
Hopefully your dad helps
out around the house, too!
Mama has 43 husbands, so if you count her
plus us and our fathers, it's 129 people.
Huh?
How is that even possible?
Some of my older brothers and sisters
already have children of their own, too.
So if you include them,
the total's even higher.
Do you want to know something else?
Almost all the Big Mom pirates
are our blood relatives.
Talk about a Big Mom.
So anyway, Pudding, have you
and Sanji met each other yet?
I...
yeah, but just once.
His eyebrows are rather strange,
but he's a very kind and gentle man.
Flower, flower!
Sometimes his eyes turn into hearts,
but he taught me so
much about making sweets
that I don't really mind things like that.
Flower, flower!
We like the same things,
and he's so manly!
And I hear his legs are black,
but it's all the same to me.
He is cool, huh?
You know that's not why
they call him Black Lake.
Yep, that's our Sanji.
There's lots of awesome things about him.
Wait, I recognize that expression.
You love him, don't you?
You're in love with Sanji?
Be honest with us.
Oh, why?
I shouldn't say.
But then, uh, Mama's
decision can't be overturned.
If I chose my husband,
then, well, he would be.
Oh, that's great.
I like Sanchi, too.
We're twinsies.
Oh, no, I can't say it out loud.
So Sanchi's engaged to
a darling young lady?
And for once it isn't someone
who rejects all his advances?
If I had eyes, they'd
be heart-shaped, too.
I'm sorry, but I think
we'd better tie her up.
She's clearly going to
tell them where we are
and if they find us here
on the outer islands?
And there's no way we'll
make it to where Sanji is.
You can't treat her like that. Stop it.
We have to keep her quiet somehow
Don't forget that girl
is a daughter of big mom.
Yeah, I know But she's
obviously afraid of her too.
Which is why she'll tell her!
But we can't know that for sure!
You gotta pipe down!
Excuse me
If I try, I can abandon
my feelings for Sanji.
I can let him go.
The people of Toto Land.
They gave us their blessing.
Celebrating the same goes
for the Vinsmoke family
and Mama's really looking
forward to the wedding!
Cake no one can disobey
an order from her so
I knew I couldn't marry
for love despite that.
I've dreamed about it since I was little I
wondered about my soulmate
what he'd be like? You know?
Then one day, I got to meet my Sanji.
Huh?
I was surprised the groom
was someone so wonderful.
But right before the end of our
meeting, he told me something.
I really would like to marry
you, but I'm afraid I just can't.
Because I want to go back
to be with my friends.
What?
Sanchi rejected a girl?
Oh, wow.
If he said no to you, then
he must really love our crew.
And that feeling is obviously mutual.
Because you're all here now.
I mean, you are risking your lives
by traveling to Toto Land to get him.
No matter what Mama says, I can't marry
Sanji if that isn't what he wants.
That'd be awful.
But more than that,
It's clear to me now how
important he is to his crewmates.
So I can't take him away.
After all, the heart wants what
the heart wants, as they say.
Which is why, if this is what
Sanji's heart wants, then I'm in.
You should take this route.
It's the one path you can
use to avoid Mama's eye.
Only her children know about it.
And that leads to Sanji?
If you follow this map, eventually
you should reach Whole Cake Island.
But Mama won't let him
slip through her fingers.
I say we rendezvous tomorrow
at the coast right here, okay?
I promise I'll bring Sanji
there whatever the cost.
Let's all work together.
You don't mind?
Don't you think Big Mom will punish you?
Mama and I are family,
so don't worry about me.
It's worse for you.
You're in hostile territory.
Puddin.
My dear, this must be painful for you.
You and Sanji care about each other.
This is the right thing.
Warms my heart.
That is if I had one.
This is heartbreaking for me.
But I'll just try and
focus on my future suitor.
Maybe he'll be even more incredible.
Oh, you're such a gracious young lady.
It's hard to believe you're
the child of someone so scared.
This is great, thanks!
I'm happy to help out.
Lady Pudding, your
escort is ready for you.
One moment.
I'm in the middle of something.
I'll be right out.
Forgive me, my lady, but you must
stop working until after the wedding.
Stop working?
But I have customers.
You need to make preparations.
Oh, hey, it's you.
I've got the groceries you ordered.
You're welcome to pick them up.
Food, finally!
You got all that?
We'll be okay. Thanks a lot.
Chocolate burgers, too?
We have enough, Luffy. Now let's go.
Peckham's is waiting.
But I want one really bad.
Chocolate pasta.
Chocolate fried chicken.
Stop looking at other stuff.
We have to go.
Anyone see him?
I don't think so.
Well, this is unusual.
Is he pooping?
Check the toilet. Hey!
There's a message in the bathroom!
Huh?
Turn back!
What the heck?
Did Peckhams write that?
No one else was aboard.
Were we attacked?
Where'd Peckhams go?
You think he got abducted?
Just speculating but maybe we've been
found out regardless this is quite serious.
So they're trying to tell us that if we
don't turn back something bad will happen!
All right everyone keep
that in mind i guess.
Okay let's go.
This is starting to get real good.
Fire!
All done here? Yes, sir.
Good.
Let's go.
You killed my wife.
You killed my children.
You left my country in ruins.
You germ of bastards.
I'll send you to hell
where you belong, dammit!
Wall.
I can't believe this took four hours.
My brother's wedding is soon.
I'm in a hurry.
I don't give a damn about your family.
Or your war.
They're both irrelevant.
Well, we're done.
I can't believe these pathetic countries.
Kept this up for two whole years?
Got the commission?
You bet I did.
They saved our country.
The world may call them demons?
But they're wrong.
To us. Well.
These are angels.
Put down your weapons, men.
At long last, the war is over.
We love you, Jarba!
Jarba, number six, thank you.
Jarba, Jarba, Jarba, Jarba.
The wedding's in three days.
We can make it to Whole Cake
Island in two days, easily.
What about Sanji?
He's already here.
Really? Perfect.
I can't wait to see him.
Is that a joke?
We'll be there soon.
Kali!